[{"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Go 'head", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I'm tellin' you, she'll be there, I know she'll be there", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "How you gonna catch anybody alone at a dance?... I don't know if she'll be there alone... She'll probably be there with her girlfriends or something", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How you gonna catch anybody alone at a dance?... I don't know if she'll be there alone... She'll probably be there with her girlfriends or something", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Nah, she don't go with nobody. She's only 15 years old", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Where you going at this hour", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You fuckin' worm, if you're going out, I'm going out", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "All right, my friend, you're being talked about as the top middleweight contender. Do you think another victory over my friend will get you a shot at the title", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, the word is to get a title shot you have to cooperate with the people who control boxing, in that place. And they're saying that you don't cooperate", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " They robbed us! Those fuckin' judges", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You won and was robbed! You didn't do nothin' wrong", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Don't tell me", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You're not interested in him", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " C'mon, my friend", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Never felt better", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What did I say", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I never noticed his face", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I dunno. We're working on it. He's training at the camp now", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "We're gonna get our shot", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Try to understand, my friend. my friend's got a lotta aggravation. He's been a top contender too long", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "And you're drinking with them right now", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend, if there was anything funny, I would tell you", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sure, I'll keep an eye on her", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Now the fight's off the books altogether. my friend couldn't get a bet down on this fight. Some people are saying you're going into the tank", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I want to believe you, my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What the fuck they want? I took the dive. They want me to fall down too? I don't fall down for nobody. I never went down in my life. my friend, what do I gotta do? Crawl on my hands and knees? I made an asshole of myself in the fuckin' Garden! All the newspaper writers make fun of me. I'm the bum of the year. All I want is a shot. Just a fuckin' shot. What do I gotta do? I'll do anything", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, except fall down. That's right", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Except fall down like a normal person", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "All right, you don't wanna fall down, so now you gotta take a rest. So, you enjoy the suspension. 'Cause there's nothin' you can do about it. Let the Commissioner and the D.A. jerk you around. So you wait", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "  Hey, you don't say goodbye to him like that", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " You don't kiss like that. Hello and goodbye, that's all you do", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What did I do", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "All I did..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Ain't a cheek ever good enough for you? I never even kissed Mama on the mouth", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well, that's what I mean", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "When", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Nothin'. my friend was out of line. He was drunk or somethin', I dunno. Anyway, the windup was I gave him a beatin'. my friend called me down, and we straightened it out. It's all forgotten about", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Why didn't you tell me about it", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Didn't it have nothin' to do with me", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No, I just told you what happened", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend, no. I just explained the whole thing to you. It was just between me and my friend, if it had anything to do with you and my friend, I woulda told you about it", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " I did keep an eye..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Whadda ya mean", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Nine o'clock", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yeah. At night", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "OK. Talk", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What do I say to him? Call him up on the phone and say,", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Didn't you also wish to sell the Championship Belt, Mr. my friend", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "But where's the belt", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "That's it. Those are the jewels that were in the belt", "docId": "raging_bull.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You want the jewels or the belt", "qsentId": 54}]